(Dr Lorvis:)Uh, I'm being implacable
and relentless.
(Amy:)Isn't she lucky?
(Dr Lorvis:)She keeps sending me
mixed signals.
But I-I think we both
want the same thing.
(Amy:)What's that?
(Dr Lorvis:)Unconditional love.
(Amy:)I guess that's
all anybody wants.
(Dr Lorvis:)I guess so.
(Amy:)Well, I hope you get it.
(Man:)One Mississippi,
two Mississippi.
(Leonard:)Next game,
let's switch helmets.
(Sheldon:)No, I'd look silly
in that helmet.
I-I can't take these.
Well, why not?
(Dr Lorvis:)I mean, you want what I want.
(Dr Lorvis:)And we had
two wonderful Mississippis.
(Amy:)But what about
the other girl?
(Dr Lorvis:)Oh, right.
(stammers)
(Dr Lorvis:)I'll tell her
(Dr Lorvis:)we should just be friends.